OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/020
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Private agreements: Code nos.K7417-K7532 (Box 52)
  - 7513, 1993-2006 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    1/1993 - 8/2006
  - 7521, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    9/14/2004
  - 7526, 1998-2004 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    9/14/1998 - 9/14/2004
  - 7532, 2002-2005 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    March 15 2002 - March 14 2005
  - Folder List Index Box # 52 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Private agreements: Code nos.7509-7592 (Box 53)
  - 7509, 1995-2001 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    7/1995 - 6/2001
  - 7509, 1976-1990 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    5/1976 - 6/1990
  - 7513, 1973-1992 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    3/1973 - 12/1992
  - 7520, 1990-2000 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    3/1990 - 2/2000
  - 7524, 1993-2001 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    10/1993 - 10/2001
  - 7525, 1970-1989 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    4/1970 - 6/1989
  - 7526, 1971-1989 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    5/1971 - 9/1989
  - 7528, 1976-1995 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    8/1976 - 5/1995
  - 7530, 1979-1985 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    6/1979 - 6/1985
  - 7542, 1994-2002 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    6/1994 - 5/2002
  - 7560, 1994-1997 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    6/1994 - 5/1997
  - 7592, 1983-1998 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    12/1983 - 2/1998
  - Folder List Index Box # 53 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Private agreements: Code nos.8010-8066 (Box 54)
  - 8010, 1989-2001 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    7/1989 - 10/2001
  - 8014, 1995-2000 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    7/1995 - 6/2000; Hahnemann University
  - 8016, 1983-2003 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    Group Health Cooperative; 6/1983 - 6/2003
  - 1800, 1975-1993 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    Amoco Oil; 1/1975 - 2/1993
  - 1801, 1977-1993 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    Amoco Oil (Manufacturing and Guards); 1/1977 - 1/1993
  - 1806, 1975-1993 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    Chevron; 1/1975 - 2/1993
  - 1807, 1971-1990 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    Exxon Co USA; 3/1971 - 3/1990
  - 8020, 1995-2001 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    League of Voluntary Hospital; 12/1995 - 10/2001
  - 8029, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    Great Atlantic Pacific and Tea; 11/1995
  - 8031, 1989-1998 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    Albert Einstein College of Medicine; 9/1989 - 9/1998
  - 8032, 1996-2003 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    Health Care Centers; 3/1996 - 2/2003
  - 8038, 1984-1996 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    Hospitals; 10/1984 - 6/1996
  - 8047, 1994-2002 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    Legal Aid Society; 9/1994 - 9/2002
  - 8056, 1998-2002 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    Sunshine Biscuits; 9/1998 - 10/2002
  - 8066, 1989-1995 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    Association General Contractors; 5/1989 - 4/1995
  - Folder List Index Box # 54 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Public agreements: Code nos.830815-840022 (Box 55)
  - 830815, 1999-2002 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - 830816, 2001-2004 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    San Francisco Unified School District
  - 830817, 2001-2004 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - 830818, 1999-2002 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Parkway School District Board of Education
  - 830819, 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    Worcester School Committee
  - 830821, 2003-2006 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    School Board of Alachua County
  - 830822, 2001-2004 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - 830823, 2003-2006 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - 830829, 2003-2006 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    Billings Public Schools
  - 830827, 1993-1994 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - 830829, 2003-2006 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - 830832, 2002-2005 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    West Contra Costa Unified School District
  - 830835, 2002-2005 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    Long beach Unified School District
  - 830836, 2003-2006 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    University of California
  - 830837, 2005-2006 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    State of California
  - 830838, 2003-2005 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - 830839, 2003-2005 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - 830840, 2001-2004 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - 830841, 2003-2004 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - 830844, 2002-2005 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    University of California (RN's Unit 7)
  - 830847, 2003-2006 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    School Board of Broward County
  - 830850, 2003-2006 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    Seattle Community College District 6
  - 830851, 2003-2005 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    City of Kansas City, Missouri
  - 840002, 1994-2004 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    Alameda Contra Costa Transit
  - 840003, 2000-2006 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    Los Angeles County Metropolitan Transit Authority
  - 840009, 2000-2002 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - 840010, 1997-2001 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    Port Authority of Allegheny County
  - 840011, 2002-2004 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    Chicago Park District
  - 840012, 1995-2003 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    City of New York Department of Corrections
  - 840013, 1995-1997 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    Oregon Health Sciences University
  - 840014, 2002-2005 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    Miami-Dade
  - 840015, 2003-2004 (Box 55, Folder 32)
    Board of Education School District 189
  - 840016, 2001-2003 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - 840017, 1994-1995 (Box 55, Folder 34)
    Board of Directors Little Rock School District
  - 840018, 2002-2005 (Box 55, Folder 35)
    Mass Transit Administration
  - 840019, 2000-2003 (Box 55, Folder 36)
    Chicago Transit Authority
  - 840020, 2002-2004 (Box 55, Folder 37)
    University of Oregon
  - 840021, 2002-2004 (Box 55, Folder 38)
    Ventura County Community College
  - 840022, 2003-2006 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Folder List Index Box # 55 (Box 55, Folder 40)
- Private agreements: Code nos.K5778-K6054 (Box 56)
  - 5778, 2000-2004 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    August 7 2000 - August 6 2004
  - 5782, 2002-2006 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - 5799, 2003-2006 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    November 9 2003 - November 4 2006
  - 5801, 2002-2005 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    November 30 2002 - November 29 2005
  - 5805, 2001-2004 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    August 8 2001 - June 30 2004
  - 6000, 2001-2004 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    9/5/2001 - 8/14/2004
  - 6001, 2002-2005 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    4/1/2002 - 4/1/2005
  - 6007, 2000-2003 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - 6008, 2001-2005 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    April 1 2001 - September 30 2005
  - 6012, 2003-2006 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - 6013, 2002-2005 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    December 2 2002 - December 1 2005
  - 6014, 2001-2004 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    2/23/2001 - 10/31/2004
  - 6015, 2002-2005 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - 6016, 2003-2006 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    May 26 2003 - May 25 2006
  - 6017, 2002-2005 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - 6018, 2000-2004 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    December 3 2000 - December 2 2004
  - 6025, 2002-2006 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    May 13 2002 - May 7 2006
  - 6027, 2002-2005 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    5/1/2002 - 4/30/2005
  - 6028, 1999-2002 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    May 1 1999 - April 30 2002
  - 6030, 2003-2005 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    1/1/2003 - 12/31/2005
  - 6043, 2001-2005 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    October 16 2001 - October 15 2005
  - 6044, 2001-2006 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - 6045, 2002-2005 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    April 1 2002 - April 1 2005
  - 6055, 2000-2006 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - 6050, 2002-2004 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    April 1 2002 - December 31 2004
  - 6054, 2000-2004 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    June 6 2000 - June 1 2004
- Private agreements: Code nos.8651-8992 (Box 57)
  - 8651, 2002-2006 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    8/1/2002 - 7/31/2006
  - 8669, 2002-2006 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - 8676, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    August 1 2003 - July 31 2006
  - 8677, 2001-2006 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - 8684, 2001-2006 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    October 1 2001 - September 30 2006
  - 8699, 2001-2006 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    April 1 2001 - March 31 2006
  - 8707, 2002-2006 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - 8724, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    6/1/2003 - 6/1/2006
  - 8727, 2002-2006 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - 8728, 2002-2006 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - 8730, 2001-2006 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - 8740, 2001-2006 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - 8744, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - 8764, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - 8775, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - 8781, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - 8783, 2002-2006 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - 8796, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - 8832, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    May 1 2003 - April 30 2006
  - 8844, 1993-2008 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    6/1993 - 5/31/2008
  - 8868, 2001-2006 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - 8872, 2001-2006 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - 8887, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - 8900, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - 8902, 2004-2006 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - 8912, 2004-2006 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    2004-2006
  - 8913, 2004-2006 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - 8934, 2004-2006 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - 8949, 2000-2003 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    4/2000 - 3/2003
  - 8959, 2004-2006 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - 8963, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - 8966, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    September 1 2003 - December 31 2006
  - 8967, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - 8973, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - 8974, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - 8978, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - 8986, 2000-2006 (Box 57, Folder 37)
    May 1 2000 - April 30 2006
  - 8988, 2002-2006 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - 8990, 2003-2006 (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - 8992, 2002-2006 (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - Folder List Index Box # 57 (Box 57, Folder 41)
- Private agreements: Code nos.8069-8339 (Box 58)
  - 8069, 1993-1998 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    12/1993 - 8/1998
  - 8101, 1971-1991 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    4/1971 - 7/1991
  - 8101, 1995-2003 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    5/1995 - 5/2003
  - 8122, 1990-1993 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    4/1990 - 3/1993
  - 8147, 1965-1993 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    4/1965 - 3/1993
  - 8180, 1995-1999 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    3/1995 - 3/1999
  - 8182, 1974-1991 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    8/1974 - 6/1991
  - 8190, 1997-2001 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    12/1997 - 10/2001
  - 8194, 1970-1987 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    6/1970 - 5/1987
  - 8195, 1992-2004 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    5/1992 - 1/2004
  - 8210, 1993-1996 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    6/1993 - 6/1996
  - 8211, 1987-1996 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    7/1987 - 7/1996
  - 8232, 2000-2008 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    4/2000 - 3/2008
  - 8300, 1987-1999 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    12/1987 - 8/1999
  - 8326, 1962-1992 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    2/1962 - 6/1992
  - 8339, 1990-2003 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    2/1990 - 12/2003
  - Folder List Index Box # 58 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- Public agreements: Code nos.811881-820224 (Box 59)
  - 811881, 1994-1995 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - 811882, 1990-1993 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Famint Home Care Service
  - 820009, 2002-2004 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - 820013, 2001-2004 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - 820024, 2003-2006 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    LA County Employment Association of Los Angeles
  - 820027, 2004-2006 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - 820044, 2003-2004 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    Heads of Department Offices of Bureau City Administration
  - 820048, 2002-2005 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - 820073, 2002-2005 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    Department of Human Services
  - 820074, 2003-2005 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    Prince George County Maryland
  - 820075, 2000-2002 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    AFSCME-CIO Council 67 and LO. 44
  - 820076, 2004-2005 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    Board of School Commissioner
  - 820077, 2001-2004 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - 820079, 1998-1999 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    Board of Education San Diego Unified School
  - 820080, 2002-2005 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - 820081, 1999-2000 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    Board of Education of Hartford County
  - 820082, 2003-2005 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - 820084, 2003-2005 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    Minneapolis Board of Education
  - 820106, 1978-1989 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    County of Marin
  - 820145, 2003-2006 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    School Board Miami Dade County
  - 820146, 2002-2005 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    City of New Orleans
  - 820148, 2001-2003 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - 820149, 1996-2003 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - 820154, 2003-2006 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    School District Number 1 in City and County Denver and State of Colorado
  - 820155, 2000-2003 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - 820156, 2001-2004 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    Elk Grove Unified School District
  - 820157, 2001-2006 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - 820161, 2001-2004 (Box 59, Folder 28)
    County of Onondaga
  - 820175, 2003-2006 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - 820191, 2003-2006 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - 820191, 1979-1983 (Box 59, Folder 31)
    Management of County of Los Angeles
  - 820192, 2000-2003 (Box 59, Folder 32)
    Beaverton School District 48
  - 820210, 2001-2006 (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - 820211, 2000-2006 (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - 820213, 1999-2002 (Box 59, Folder 35)
    County of Niagara
  - 820215, 2003-2006 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - 820216, 2003-2006 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - 820218, 2005-2006 (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - 820219, 2003-2006 (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - 820220, 1999-2002 (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - 820218, 2001-2003 (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - 820222, 2004-2006 (Box 59, Folder 42)
    County of Los Angeles and Los Angeles Flood Control
  - 820223, 2003-2004 (Box 59, Folder 43)
    Head Department Office of Bureaus Represented
  - 820244, 2002-2005 (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - Folder List Index Box # 59 (Box 59, Folder 45)
- Private agreements: Code nos.7577-8031 (Box 60)
  - 7577, 2000-2003 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - 7706, 2002-2005 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    May 6 2002 - May 5 2005
  - 7901, 2002-2005 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    March 1 2002 - February 28 2005
  - 7904, 2002-2005 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    December 1 2002 - November 30 2005
  - 7912, 2001-2004 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - 7913 (1/3), 2001-2004 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - 7913 (2/3) (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - 7913 (3/3) (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - 7914 (1/3), 2002-2005 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - 7914 (2/3), 2002-2005 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - 7914 (3/3), 2002-2005 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - 7919, 2001-2004 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    October 17 2001 - October 16 2004
  - 7921, 2002-2005 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    February 16 2002 - February 15 2005
  - 7930, 2001-2005 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    November 1 2001 - April 30 2005
  - 7940, 2001-2005 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    1/08/2001 - 2/05/2005
  - 7943, 2001-2005 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    October 1 2001 - May 15 2005
  - 7950, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - 7951, 2002-2005 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    March 31 2002 - May 31 2005
  - 7971, 2002-2005 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    May 27 2002 - May 29 2005
  - 7982, 2002-2005 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    February 1 2002 - January 31 2005
  - 7992, 2001-2005 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    June 1 2001 - May 31 2005
  - 8005, 2002-2005 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    January 15 2002 - January 15 2005
  - 8006, 2002-2004 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    July 1 2002 - June 30 2004
  - 8007, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    September 1 2003
  - 8008, 2002-2004 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    January 1 2002 - December 31 2004
  - 8012, 2002-2005 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - 8017, 2002-2004 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - 8031, 1998-2001 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    October 1 1998 - October 31 2001
  - Folder List Index Box # 60 (Box 60, Folder 29)
- Private agreements: Code nos.K1475-K2610 (Box 61)
  - 1475, 2000-2006 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    9/1/2000 - 8/31/2006
  - 1476, 1998-2000 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    January 1 1998 - December 31 2000
  - 1480, 2001-2004 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    August 5 2001 - August 7 2004
  - 1631, 2002-2005 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    May 15 2002 - May 14 2005
  - 1644, 2003-2006 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - 1683, 2003 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    May 20 2003
  - 1902, 2003-2006 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    8/20/2003 - 7/22/2006
  - 1903, 2005-2006 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    June 8 2005 - July 23 2006
  - 1906, 2004-2006 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    August 20 2004 - July 22 2006
  - 1909, 1997-2003 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    7/24/1997 - 6/23/2003
  - 1913, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    August 1 1997
  - 1926, 2003-2006 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - 1927, 2002-2005 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - 1934, 2003-2006 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    July 6 2003 - July 22 2006
  - 1938, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    February 27 2004
  - 1939, 2004-2006 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    April 7 2004 - July 22 2006
  - 2303, 2000-2005 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    October 1 2000 - September 30 2005
  - 2308, 2002-2006 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    January 21 2002 - January 20 2006
  - 2351, 2002-2005 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    April 1 2002 - March 31 2005
  - 2357, 2002-2005 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - 2453, 2002-2006 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - 2500, 1993-1999 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    September 1 1993 - August 31 1999
  - 2504, 1999-2006 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    November 1 1999 - February 28 2006
  - 2505, 2001-2006 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - 2506, 2000-2005 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    August 31 2000 - August 31 2005
  - 2529, 1999-2002 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    May 3 1999 - May 3 2002
  - 2534, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    October 26 2001
  - 2539, 1999-2004 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    8/1/1999 - 8/1/2004
  - 2544, 1999-2004 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - 2589, 2001-2004 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - 2592, 2001-2006 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    May 31 2001 - May 31 2006
  - 2610, 2001-2006 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Folder List Index Box # 61 (Box 61, Folder 33)
- Private agreements: Code nos.8538-8722 (Box 62)
  - 8538, 2000-2003 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    San Francisco Electrical Contractors Association (inside)
  - 8545, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Bricklayers Trade Agreement
  - 8551, 1997-2000 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Employing Bricklayers Association of Delaware Valley
  - 8554, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Mason Contractors Exchange of Southern California
  - 8556, 1999-2002 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    Cement League
  - 8557, 1997-2000 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Building Restoration Contractors Association (pointers, caulkers)
  - 8559, 1999-2002 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    General Contractors Association of NY
  - 8567, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Walls and Ceilings Contractors Association of Greater Cincinnati
  - 8568, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Independent Building Agreement (was BCA)
  - 8570, 1999-2004 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    Allied Construction and AGC
  - 8572, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    Sheet Metal Contractors Association of Philadelphia
  - 8575, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    Sheet Metal and Air Conditioning Contractors Association of NYC
  - 8577, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    Allied Building Metal Industries (structural)
  - 8578, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    Allied Building Metal Industries (ornamental)
  - 8581, 2000-2005 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    Excavators, Inc.
  - 8582, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    Iron Worker Employers Council
  - 8585, 2001-2002 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    National Mechanical and Plumbing Equipment/System Service and Maintenance
  - 8586, 1999-2003 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    Kern, Inyo and Mono Counties Sheet Metal and AC Contractors
  - 8587, 1998-2003 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    National Pneumatic Control Systems Install and Service
  - 8589, 2001-2005 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    National Service and Maintenance Agreement
  - 8592, 2000-2003 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    Northeastern States Boilermaker Employers
  - 8593, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    Connecticut Construction Industries Association
  - 8594, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    Keystone Building Contractors Association (21 counties)
  - 8595, 2004-2005 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    AGC, TX - Houston and Construction Employers Association
  - 8596, 1998-2005 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    Master Builders Association of Western PA
  - 8604, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    Ohio Contractors Association
  - 8605, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - 8609, 1999-2005 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    Chicagoland Sheet Metal Contractors Association
  - 8615, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    Maryland heavy and Highway Contractors Association
  - 8631, 1999-2004 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    Site Improvement Association
  - 8634, 2001-2005 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    Construction Employers Association
  - 8637, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 32)
    Colorado Statewide Laborers Independent
  - 8639, 2001-2005 (Box 62, Folder 33)
    Plumbing Industry Council
  - 8641, 2000-2005 (Box 62, Folder 34)
    Mason Contractors Association of St. Louis
  - 8652, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 35)
    Construction Industry Council et al
  - 8653, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 36)
    Sheet Metal Contractors Association of Central PA
  - 8661, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 37)
    National Transient Lodge Articles of Agreement
  - 8663, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 38)
    IUOE Independent 2002
  - 8666, 2000-2003 (Box 62, Folder 39)
    AGC, MI and Independents-Greater Detroit
  - 8667, 2000-2005 (Box 62, Folder 40)
    Johnson Controls
  - 8673, 2000-2005 (Box 62, Folder 41)
    Elevator Manufacturers Association of New York
  - 8675, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 42)
    Mechanical Contractors Association of NY (steamfitters)
  - 8679, 2001-2003 (Box 62, Folder 43)
    Pennsylvania Heavy and Highway Contractors Association
  - 8680, 1999-2004 (Box 62, Folder 44)
    Wisconsin Transportation Employers Council
  - 8682, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 45)
    Construction Industries Counties of Westchester and Hudson Valley
  - 8690, 2000-2004 (Box 62, Folder 46)
    National Electrical Contractors Association
  - 8691, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 47)
    Mechanical Contractors Association Metro Washington
  - 8692, 1999-2003 (Box 62, Folder 48)
    West Virginia Contractors Bargaining Association
  - 8697, 2000-2003 (Box 62, Folder 49)
    Eastern Contractors Association
  - 8701, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 50)
    IUOE Master Agreement
  - 8702, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 51)
    National Electrical Contractors Association Hudson Valley
  - 8703, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 52)
    Lighting and Electrical Maintenance Association
  - 8705, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 53)
    Cement and Concrete Workers and Independent Employers
  - 8708, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 54)
    Mechanical Contractors Association of Metro Washington
  - 8710, 1997-2002 (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - 8712, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 56)
    AGC, MI and Great Lakes Fabricators and Erectors
  - 8714, 2002-2005 (Box 62, Folder 57)
    New Jersey Steel Association
  - 8717, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 58)
    General Building Contractors Association
  - 8719, 2001-2004 (Box 62, Folder 59)
    Great Lakes Fabricators and Erectors Association
  - 8721, 2001-2005 (Box 62, Folder 60)
    Mason Contractors Association of Cleveland
  - 8722, 2000-2004 (Box 62, Folder 61)
    Mechanical Contractors Association of Cleveland
  - Folder List Index Box # 62 (Box 62, Folder 62)
- Public agreements: Code nos.800357-810051 (Box 63)
  - 800407, 2002-2005 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - 800408, 1996-1999 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    July 1 1996 - June 30 1999
  - 800409, 1993-2007 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    12/1993 - 12/2007
  - 800410, 1994-2004 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    9/1994 - 12/2004
  - 800411, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    9/2005
  - 800412, 1999-2004 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    July 1 1999 - June 30 2004
  - 800415, 2000-2002 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    January 1 2000 - December 31 2002
  - 800416, 1999-2003 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    1999 - 7/1/2003
  - 800417, 2003-2005 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - 800419, 2004-2005 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    7/1/2004 - 6/30/2005
  - 800422, 2002-2005 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    December 14 2002 - November 15 2005
  - 800423, 2002-2006 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    October 1 2002 - September 30 2006
  - 800425, 2003-2005 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - 800426, 1991-1994 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    July 1 1991 - June 30 1994
  - 800427, 2003-2005 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - 800428, 2003-2005 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - 800429, 2003-2006 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - 800430, 2005-2006 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    July 1 2005 - June 30 2006
  - 810007, 2001-2005 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    2001 - 12/31/2005
  - 810013, 2002-2005 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    9/1/2002 - 8/31/2005
  - 810032, 2005-2006 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    July 1 2005 - September 30 2006
  - 810032, 2000-2002 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    11/15/2000 - 6/30/2002
  - 810041, 2000-2002 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    August 1 2000 - October 31 2002
  - 810051, 2000-2005 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    2000 - 6/30/2005
  - Folder List Index Box # 63 (Box 63, Folder 25)
- Public agreements: Code nos.810064-810302 (Box 64)
  - 810064, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    July 1 2002
  - 810084, 2004-2005 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    2004 - 6/30/2005
  - 810084, 2002-2003 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - 810086, 1997-2001 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    6/1997 - 6/2001
  - 810089, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    October 15 1992
  - 810108, 1995-1997 (Box 64, Folder 6)